Dad where are we now?
null
Nikkalouka!
What was it called yesterday?
Nouk colook!
And the day before yesterday?
Nakkikika!
Now we have traveled by bus from Kiruna to Nikkaloukta
And here is cold, but it does not rain at least so it is nice.
Exited?
Let's Take Photos!
Eh, my camera inside my rain jacket whole
The road to
The mountain station where we are now
It is twelve kilometers of rain.
All we have is wet!
My sleeping bag is so wet
That I could squeeze it out and it would run.
I don't know what to sleep at night.
I will freeze like an ass.
Do you hear how it rains?
This..
So ... stressful!
I am not built for such challenges
I feel like a spoiled Stockholmer - and I am after all
Largely.
But shit what it took time!
Now it is almost twelve o'clock
At night.
And I think the last time I talked to you so was six o'clock in the evening
Herrejävstagud!
But ... should you see it from the bright side
So we will hike in type 9 kilometers, and then we will go boat
It will be very nice because I have brutal pain
In my right foot.
Here's how you can do!
So you have to do when you know the road will be wet
And you will need to go in the wet with anyway one foot
But the other foot cannot have to tie on
It then dies
Now you are well!
- Yes, I long for a shower, otherwise it's good
Here we have my backpack too.
I look very much forward to putting it on my back
null
See you along the way, bye!